레즐리가 "광속 인간 레너드"라고 별명까지 지어줬지
For which she awarded him the nickname "Speed of Light Leonard."
페니랑 저녁 식사 3시간
And the three hour dinner with Penny.
앉은 시간만 치면 2시간 반이겠지만
Which would have been two and a half if they ordered the souffle when they sat down.
등비수열을 적용하면
Based on the geometric progression,
20분 뒤에 스테파니랑 헤어지게 돼 있다고
his relationship with Stephanie should have ended after 20 minutes.
나도 그 정도 계산은 돼 27일 나누기 12의 n승이잖아
Yes, I'm aware of the math. Y equals 27 days over 12 to the nth.
문제는 그대로야
The issue remains.
피할 수 없는 헤어짐을 어떻게 넘어가냐는 거지
How do we circumvent his inevitable rejection?
스테파니한테 매력적으로 보이려면
If you want to guarantee his appeal to Stephanie,
지구 상의 남자란 남자는 다 죽이는 게 제일 좋은 방법일 거야
your best bet would be to kill all the other men on the planet.